eroticmonkey.ch 2019-12-26

# Privacy Policy

  1. **GENERAL:**   
This Privacy Policy applies to EroticMonkey.ch web site and various related services associated with the website (together referred to as this "Site"). This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect through the Site, how we use that information, and what choices you have surrounding use of your information. 

The Site contains links to other web sites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of any companies or individuals that EM Services does not control, or any web sites that you link to from the Site. You should use caution and review the privacy policies of any sites that you visit from ours to learn more about their information and privacy practices.

Please take a few moments to read this agreement. By accessing the Site, you agree to accept the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and are aware that our policies may evolve in the future as indicated below. 

  2. **WHAT WE COLLECT:**   
In various places on the Site, we collect personally identifiable information, such as your name, postal address, telephone number, e-mail address, information you provide as part of your user profile or other information that can be used to identify you or contact you ("PII"). For example, we collect this information when you register for membership, sign up for an e-mail newsletter and when you request technical support. From time to time in the future we may offer additional features, services and promotional opportunities that would require you to submit additional PII to participate. 

We also collect "Anonymous Information" such as your IP address, the type of browser you use, the pages on the Site that you visit.   
Like many Internet sites, we also use "cookies" to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer and is stored on your hard drive. When you visit the Site, the cookie identifies your user credentials to us so that you do not have to re-register each time you visit. We also use cookies to measure the traffic to our site and its different services and features. 

We do not intend that children will use our sites. We do not solicit or knowingly collect information from children under 13 years old, nor will we knowingly accept registration from them. 

  3. **HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT:**   
We use PII that you provide us to process registration information for membership purposes and to provide e-mail updates. 

We use information that is not personally identifiable to determine how people use our web site and its services. Analyzing this data also allows us to improve the offerings on and performance of the Site. 

  4. **How we share information:**   
We will never sell, rent or loan your PII without you expressed written consent. We sometimes use third parties to help with some of the services available through the Site, such as third party software and service vendors, partners and consultants. When we supply PII to these third parties, we require them to use it only for the function they are helping us with. 

We aggregate the Anonymous Information that we collect and may exchange it with others who are interested in our services. 

We will disclose PII as required by law, or if in our judgment it is necessary to protect our company or our users from loss or liability. If we merge with or are acquired by another company, the resulting combined company will use the information you have provided as described in this policy. If we cease operation, your information may be transferred to and used by another company that offers similar or related products or services. While we cannot predict a great deal about such an unlikely event, we would hope this could provide you continuity of service. 

  5. **What choices you have:**   
When you register for membership at the Site, you agree to receive e-mail updates related to the Site. Moreover, we reserve the right to communicate with you on matters we consider especially important. If you do not agree to receive such periodic communications from EM Services, then you may not register with the Site. 
  6. **Making changes:**   
You may review some of the PII we have on file by logging into the Site. You may directly modify or delete information that is incorrect online or by contacting EM Services via e-mail at EMAIL ADDRESS. 

Since Anonymous Information is not identifiable as originating with you, it cannot be reviewed or changed by you. 

We may change this policy from time to time. While we will usually indicate major changes by notice on our site, please check here from time to time to see if there is a revised policy posted. 

  7. **Postings:**   
If you register to use our bulletin boards or user forums, please remember that anything you post is publicly available. Your profile will also be available to other users of such services. 
  8. **Security:**   
We keep PII you provide on servers that are protected by firewalls and other technological means against intrusion or unauthorized access. They are located in a physically secure facility, and only our employees and agents with a need to know the information are given access. While no amount of security can give a perfect guarantee, you can have a high degree of confidence that the personally identifiable information you give us is protected from unauthorized access and use. We rely on you to select passwords that cannot be guessed easily and to safeguard those passwords from disclosure. Please contact us if you have any information regarding unauthorized use of the Site. 
  9. **Contact.:**   
If you have questions about the use of your personal information, our policies about privacy or any of the contents within this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: 

info@eroticmonkey.ch   
ImGate s.r.o namesti pratelstvi 1518/2, hostivai, 10200 Praha 10, ID 06832946
